My 10+ team of direct deals will
come on your screen. Add these stocks. Whether to trade or
not, your financial advisor will
tell you better. ICICI Lombard is gaining
good market share. May's premium data.
Signature Global
acquired land in Gurgaon. In contrast, it is
selling its land in Mumbai's Kanjur Marg to NIT for a good amount. Indus
Towers is in the red. Keep an eye on
vodafoneidea.com. I will
start with cement stocks. Ambuja has
acquired Penna Industries located in Andhra Pradesh and Telangana, after which
Brook Ridge's review is good. There is cheap
valuation. You
may see momentum here somewhere today. Apart from this,
other takeover targets in the cement pack, which the market is
assuming, may react
positively today. India Cement and Orient Cement.
So, I am taking these three cement stocks in the green.
Apart from this, Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL) and
GRSC, yesterday the Defense Minister
said that
let us assume an export target of Rs 50-100 crore for defense companies.  So, the
focus will be on export markets, there will be
focus on domestic production, that is why I am
taking all these defense stocks in green. Apart from this, Havells
India has announced a capex of 50 to 60 crores.
In the air conditioning segment,
NALCO has been allotted a big mine in Odisha with a
capacity of 35 MTPA. There, Landmark Cars Ltd has
announced a capex of 3000 crores
in Maharashtra and the
stock is quite attractive, so I kept these 10 stocks on
my radar.
Okay, so these were the teams and it was 464 at 10.
We are preparing to open around yesterday's highest T.
Rajesh ji, tell me which two of your
trends are there among these teams. Very good morning,
if you look at Ashi ji's team, the
best chart is I think
keep an eye on IC Lord, there is a consolidation and a
break after the consolidation, so I think at
least its target should be. It is
opening at 1689 points, so obviously
I will have to change the stop loss.  Stop loss will be at
1650. Keep the strategy and buy for the target of 1750.
If we see Neeraj ji's team,
sorry if we see Yatin ji's team, then the
best one is Hales. I like the overall Rajeev
space, like talking about Volta,
talking about Hales, the space is good, so
if we look at Hales today, I feel that there is a
breakout after consolidation.
Keep a stop loss of 18644 and
set a target in front of it, from 1900 to 1920. So,
this is a one second buy tomorrow,
ok.